## ALDO ALFREDO MOLOAN

## **Junior Software Developer**

Medan, Indonesia | Phone: 085763517668 | Email: aldoalfredomsirait@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I am interested in everything about technology and always fun to creating a lot of things inside on the internet especially Mobile and Web Application. My interest in that started back in 2020 when I made an website and application that my university need. I also previously worked at Rogate Drug Store, Freshtasio and LPSI Catholic University of St. Thomas.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### LPSI Catholic University of St. Thomas - Medan, Indonesia

Junior Software Developer (Juli 2022 - Sep 2022)

- Building an Mobile Application School of Information Systems using flutter and Codeigneter 4 as a REST ful API.
- Create a web-based employee questionnaire.
- Develop a book Desain Grafis Teori dan Praktek menggunakan CorelDraw X7.
- Built App E-Report Application (Complaint Service) at the Catholic University of Santo Thomas Medan using Flutter and Firebase frameworks.
- Set Acces Point Wi-Fi at Asrama Putri Universitas Katolik Santo Thomas.

### Toko Obat Rogate - Medan, Indonesia

Office Assistant (Mei 2021 - Des 2022)

- Categorize items and records all store items (name, stock, price) to the Loyverse system
- Serving customers.

### **EDUCATION**

### Catholic University of St. Thomas (2019 - present)

**Bachelor of Computer Science** 

#### **SKILLS**

- Flutter
- Codeigneter 4
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- PHP & MySQL
- Firebase
- Design UI / UX Figma